FAKUNLE ELIJAH TAIWO

20, Ajibi Quarters, Off Gbekuba Road, Apata, Ibadan E-mail: efakunletaiwo@yahoo.com Mobile Phone: 08030770016

EMPLOYMENT PROFILE

EMPLOYER: INTERNATIONAL HEALTH MANAGEMENT SERVICE LTD

(HMO). 2, Joseph Street, Off Broad Street, Victoria Island, Lagos.

POSITION: MARKETING EXECUTIVE (South West Region)

JOB ASSIGNMENT:

Responsible for the sourcing of new clients while maintaining relationship with existing clients.

- Arrange for meetings and presentations.
- Achieve allocated sale revenue targets.
- Conduct regular market intelligent activities.
- Coordinate the Staff weekly meeting and report.
- Contribute to the development of the Company's marketing.
- Perform Administrative task.

YEAR: Oct.2015- TODATE

EMPLOYER: SPRING BANK PLC (NOW HERITAGE BANK PLC)

143, Ahmed Bellow way,

Victoria Island,

Lagos.

LOCATION: Ondo State.

Position Held: Branch Operations Manager.

JOB ASSIGNMENT:

- Coordinate branch operations.
- Cash and Cheque Management.
- Asset/Facilities Management.
- Coordinate Account and Fund transfer.
- Coordinate Administrative activities.
- Ensure customer's accounts are properly maintained and managed.
- Authorization and verification of transactions.
- Coordinate Staff meetings and report.
- Ensure compliance in operations.

YEAR: Aug. 2006- NOVEMBER, 2009.

PERSONAL DATA

Date of Birth: 23rd August, 1973

Marital Status: Married
Sex: Male
Nationality: Nigerian
State of Origin: Ekiti

Languages Spoken: Yoruba, English.

OBJECTIVES:

❖ To be a seasoned and highly competent professional.

To excel in stable, secured and satisfactory employment where dedication, faithfulness, skills and competency are efficiently utilized and highly rewarded.

CAPABILITIES:

Strong inter-personal, leadership and team building qualities, ability to work patiently and focus under pressure; Good analytical and communication skills, honest and reliable; Strong commitment to work.

CAREER SUMMARY: Possess fifteen years cognate professional Banking and Finance experience in Core banking, Accounting, Marketing, Administrative and insurance.

EDUCATION

2005 Ambrose AlliUniversityEkpoma, Edo State.

B.sc. in Business Administration.

1998 Federal Polytechnic, Ilaro, Ogun State.

Higher National Diploma (HND) Business Admin.

1994 Ondo State Polytechnic Owo

National Diploma (ND) Business Studies

1989 Okemesi Grammar School, Okemesi Ekiti

WASC/GCE O-LEVEL

PROFESSIONAL BODY:

2004 Member, chartered Institute of Banker of Nigeria (CIBN)2005 Associate Member, Nigeria Institute of Management (ANIM)

OTHER WORKING EXPERIENCE

PLACE OF WORK

1. Larex Hotel Int.

1994-1996

Account Officer
Palmgrove, Lagos

2.	Obedu Secondary School,	1999-2000	Teacher
Uromi (NYSC)			

3. Spring Bank Plc,	2000-2002	Clearing/Cash Officer
Network Office Akure		

4. Spring Bank Plc, 2002-2006 Account/Clearing Officer

Ondo

5. Shalom Investment (Microfinance) 2010-2011 Operations / Marketing Manager

6. Standard Alliance Life Assurance 2012-Sep."13 Marketing Executive

7. First Bank Insurance Ltd 2013-2015 Financial Advisor

TRAINING AND SEMINARS ATTENDED:

**	Accelerated Management Training Programme	2001	
*	Modular Training on Fraud & Prevention	2002	
*	Banking Operations Management (H. Pierson Training	2004	
*	Customer Relationship Management Seminar	2005	
*	Cash and Asset Management Seminar	2006	
**	Time and Sales Territory Management Skills (FactBase	Consulting Ltd)	2016

SKILLS:

Computer Skills on Globus & Finacle application, MS – Word, MS – Excel, MS – Power Point.

HOBBIES:Reading, Writing, sports, music, making friends **REFEREES**

1. **General (Rtd.) Olu Olorunkunle,** *C.E.O./MD, Xtadok Nig. Ltd,* Tafawa Balewa Square (TBS), Victoria Island, Lagos.

Tel: 08033933575

2. Mr. Femi Oyekunle, Retail Manager, First Bank Insurance Ltd,

Alagbaka, Akure. **Phone:** 07038141823

3. Dr A.O Adekola, Regional Manager, International Health Management Service Ltd (HMO), Ibadan.

Phone: 08085865436